Guide to the Poetry: A Magazine of Verse Records 1895-1961
University of Chicago Library
- Series II: Administrative Files, 1936-1953
  - Subseries 1: Manuscripts - Major Contributors
    - Bonner, Amy, business correspondence, May 8, 1948 - Oct. 23, 1953 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Booth, Philip (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Bordry, Paul (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Borgese, G. A. (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Bottral, Ronald (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Boulton, Inez (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Bowe, Augustine J. (Box 52, Folder 1-3)
    - Breit, Harvey (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Brinnin, J.M., Poems (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Brinnin, J.M., Other material (Box 52, Folder 6-7)
    - Brooks, Cleanth (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Brooks, Gwendolyn (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Broomell, Myron H. (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Brown, E. K. (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Brown, Harry (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Bulosan., Carlos (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Bunting, Basil (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Burch, Claire (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Burford, William (Box 52, Folder 16-17)
    - Burke, Kenneth (Box 52, Folder 18-19)
    - Bynner, Witter (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Caffrey, John SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Carruth., Hayden, Poems and Reviews (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Carruth, Hayden, Editorials (Box 52, Folder 23-24)
    - Carruth, Hayden, Correspondence (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Castleman, Marian (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Ciardi, John, Poems (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Ciardi, John, Poems and Reviews (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Ciardi, John, Correspondence to July 1948 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Ciardi, John, Correspondence July 1948 to 1953 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Cole, Thomas (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Conrad, Sherman (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Corman, Cid (Box 53, Folder 8-9)
    - Cowley, Malcolm (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Coxe, Louis (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Creekmore, Hubert (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Cummings, E. E. SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 53, Folder 13-14)
    - Cunningham, J. V. (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Curnow, Allen (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Dahlberg, Edward SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 53, Folder 17-19)
    - Daiches, David, Poetry and Correspondence SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Daiches, David, Reviews (Box 54, Folder 1-2)
    - Daly, James (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Day, Lewis C. (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - DeJong, David C. (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - De La Mare, Walter (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Denney, Reuel (Box 54, Folder 7-8)
    - Derleth, August (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Deutsch, Babette, Poems (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Deutsch, Babette, Reviews (Box 54, Folder 11-13)
    - Deutsch, Babette, Correspondence (Box 54, Folder 14-15)
    - DeVries, Peter, Works (Box 54, Folder 16-17)
    - DeVries, Peter, Correspondence (Box 54, Folder 18-19)
    - Dillon, George, Works SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Dillon, George, correspondence 1936-1946 (Box 55, Folder 1-2)
    - Dillon, George, correspondence 1947-1953 SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Dillon, George, Udell Correspondence SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 55, Folder 4-5)
    - Dilworth, Hiram Powers (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Aldington, Hilda (Doolittle) H.D. (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Doughty, LeGarde (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Duncan, Harry SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Eberhart, Richard, Poems (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Eberhart, Richard, Reviews (Box 55, Folder 11-12)
    - Eberhart, Richard, correspondence 1947 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Eberhart, Richard, correspondence 1947-1953 SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Eliot T. S. (SEE ALSO BOX 78 Folder 21 Frank Morley) SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Elton, William, Works (Box 55, Folder 16-17)
    - Elton, William, Glossary (Box 55, Folder 18-19)
    - Elton, William, Revision of Glossary (Box 56, Folder 1-2)
    - Elton, William, Correspondence (Box 56, Folder 3-4)
    - Empson, William (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Engle, Paul, Poems (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Engle, Paul,Other material (Box 56, Folder 7-8)
    - Evans, Oliver (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Everson, William (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Fearing, Kenneth (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Ferrill Thomas H. (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Ficke, Arthur D. (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Fiedler, Leslie A. (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Fitts, Dudley SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 56, Folder 15-16)
    - Fitzgerald, Robert (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Fletcher, John Gould, Poems (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Fletcher, John Gould, Reviews (Box 56, Folder 19-20)
    - Fletcher, John Gould, Correspondence SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 56, Folder 21-22)
    - Flint, R. W. (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Forgotson, E. S. Works (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - Forgotson, E.S., Correspondence (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - Fowlie, Wallace, Works (Box 57, Folder 1-3)
    - Fowlie, Wallace, Correspondence 1951 (Box 57, Folder 4-5)
    - Fowlie, Wallace, Correspondence 1952-1953 (Box 57, Folder 6-7)
    - Frank, Rachel (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Frankenberg, Lloyd (Box 57, Folder 9-10)
    - Friar, Kimon, Works (Box 57, Folder 11-12)
    - Friar, Kimon, Correspondence SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 57, Folder 13-14)
    - Frost, Robert (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Fuller, Roy (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Gardner, Isabella and Katharine Garvin (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Ghiselin, Brewster, Works (Box 57, Folder 18-19)
    - Ghiselin, Brewster, Correspondence (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Gibbs, Barbara (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - Gibson, William (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - Glaze, Andrew (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - Gogarty, Oliver St. John (Box 57, Folder 24)
    - Golffing, Francis C., Poems and Correspondence (Box 57, Folder 25-26)
    - Golffing, Francis C., Prose (Box 58, Folder 1-2)
    - Goodman, Paul, Poems (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Goodman, Paul, correspondence (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Goodman, Paul, prose SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Goodman, Paul, prose (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Graham, W. S. (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Graves, Robert (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Gregor, Arthur (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Gregory, Horace, Poems (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Gregory, Horace, Prose (Box 58, Folder 11-14)
    - Gregory, Horace, Prose (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Gregory, Horace, Correspondence (Box 58, Folder 16-17)
    - Grigson, Geoffrey (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Gustafson, Ralph (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Harper, Carol Ely (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Harper, Robert D. (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - Hart, Lawrence, Works (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - Hart, Lawrence, Correspondence (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - Hayakawa, S. I (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Hayes, Alfred (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Hays, H. R., Poems and Correspondence. SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Hays, H.R., Prose (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Healy, John Vincent, Poems and Correspondence (Box 59, Folder 5-6)
    - Healy, John Vincent, Prose (Box 59, Folder 7-8)
    - Hecht, Anthony (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Hendry, J. F. (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Herschberver, Ruth (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Heywood, Terence (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Hillyer, Robert (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Hindus, Milton (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Holmes, John (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Honig, Edward, Poems (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Honig, Edward, Other material (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Howells, Thomas SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 59, Folder 18-19)
    - Hughes, Langston (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Humphreys, Rolfe, Poems and Correspondence, SEE ALSO Subseries 3: Sub-subseries 1: Correspondence, Notes, and Mockups, June, 1939 (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Humphreys, Rolfe, Prose (Box 59, Folder 22)
    - Hutchins, Maude Phelps (Box 59, Folder 23)
    - Ingalls, Jeremy, Works (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Ingalls, Jeremy, Correspondence (Box 60, Folder 2-3)
    - Jarrell, Randall, Poems (Box 60, Folder 4-5)
    - Jarrell, Randall, Correspondence (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Jeffers, Robinson, Poems (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Jeffers, Robinson, Hungerfield (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Jeffers, Robinson, Correspondence SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Jimenez, Juan Ramon SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 60, Folder 10-11)
    - Jolas, Eugene SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Jones, Frank (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Joost, Nicholas (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Kees, Weldon, Poems (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Kees, Weldon, Other material (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Kenner, Hugh, Prose (Box 60, Folder 17-18)
    - Kenner, Hugh, Other material (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Klein, A. M. (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Koch, Vivienne (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Kreymborg, Alfred (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Kunitz, Stanley, Poems and correspondence (Box 61, Folder 1-2)
    - Kunitz, Stanley, Prose (Box 61, Folder 3-4)
    - Lang, Dilys B. (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Lattimore, Richmond (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Laughlin, James (Box 61, Folder 7-8)
    - Lechlitner, Ruth (Box 61, Folder 9-10)
    - Lee, Muna (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Lewis, H. H. (Box 61, Folder 12-13)
    - Lewis, Janet (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Lindsay, Vachel (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Loeser, Katinka (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Logan, John SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Lowe, Robert Liddell (Box 61, Folder 18-19)
    - Lowell, Robert (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Maas, Willard (Box 61, Folder 21-22)
    - MacDiarmid, Hugh (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - MacLeish, Archibald, Works (Box 61, Folder 24-25)
    - MacLeish, Archibald, Correspondence (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - MacLeish, Archibald, Correspondence SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - MacNeice, Louis (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Madge, Charles (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Mallalieu, H. B. (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Mallan, Lloyd (Box 62, Folder 4-5)
    - Manifold, John (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Marz, Roy (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Masefield, John (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Masters, Edgar Lee (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Masters, Marcia (Box 62, Folder 10-11)
    - Mayo, E. L., Poems (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Mayo, E.L., Other material (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Meredith, William (Box 62, Folder 14-15)
    - Merriam, Eve (Box 62, Folder 16-17)
    - Merrill, James (Box 62, Folder 18-19)
    - Merton, Thomas (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Merwin, W. S. (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - Miles, Josephine (Box 62, Folder 22-23)
    - Millay, Edna St. Vincent (mss all to G. Dillion, signed by Vincent) (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - Mills, Clark (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - Moore, Harry T. (Box 62, Folder 26-27)
    - Moore, Marianne (Box 62, Folder 28)
    - Moore, Merrill (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Moore, Nicholas (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Moore, Rosalie (Box 63, Folder 3-4)
    - Morse, Samuel French SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 63, Folder 5-6)
    - Morton, David (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Moses, W. R. (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Moss, Howard, Poems (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Moss, Howard, Other material (Box 63, Folder 10-11)
    - Muir, Edwin (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Nemerov, Howard (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Nerber, John, Poems (Box 63, Folder 14-15)
    - Nerber, John, Prose (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Nerber, John, Correspondence (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Nerber, John, Correspondence (Box 63, Folder 18-19)
    - Newman, Israel (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Nims, John Frederick, Poems (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Nims, John Frederick, Poems (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - Nims, John Frederick, Prose (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - Nims, John Frederick, Prose (Box 63, Folder 24-25)
    - Nims, John Frederick, Correspondence (Box 63, Folder 26-27)
    - Nims, John Frederick, Correspondence (Box 63, Folder 28-29)
    - Norse, Harold (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - North, Jessica Nelson, Poems (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - North, Jessica Nelson, Prose (Box 64, Folder 3-4)
    - North, Jessica Nelson, Correspondence (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - O’Connor, William Van, Works (Box 64, Folder 6-7)
    - O’Connor, William Van, Works (Box 64, Folder 8-9)
    - O’Connor, William Van, Correspondence (Box 64, Folder 10-11)
    - Olson, Elder (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Olson, Laurence (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Page, P. K. (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Patchens, Kenneth (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Perse, Saint-John (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Pillin, William, Poems (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Pillin, William, Correspondence (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Poster, William (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Pound, Ezra, Works (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Pound, Ezra, Correspondence (Box 64, Folder 21-22)
    - Pound, Ezra, Case against Saturday Review (Box 64, Folder 23-24)
    - Pound, Ezra, Case against Saturday Review (Box 64, Folder 25-26)
    - Pound, Ezra, Case against Saturday Review, and miscellaneous correspondence (Box 64, Folder 27-28)
    - Pratt, E. J. (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Prokosch, Frederic (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Quinn, Kerker (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Rago, Henry, Poems (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Rago, Henry, Prose (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Rago, Henry, Correspondence (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Raine, Kathleen (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Ransom, John Crowe (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Read, Herbert (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Rice, Philip Blair (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Ridler, Anne (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Rivier, Jean (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Roberts, Michael (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Roditi, Edouard, Works (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Roditi, Edouard, Works (Box 65, Folder 16-17)
    - Roditi, Edouard, Correspondence (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Roditi, Edouard, Correspondence SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 65, Folder 19-20)
    - Roethke, Theodore, Poems (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Roethke, Theodore, Prose (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Roethke, Theodore, Correspondence (Box 65, Folder 23-24)
    - Roethke, Theodore, Correspondence (Box 65, Folder 25-26)
    - Rosenberg, Harold (Box 65, Folder 27-28)
    - Rosenberger, Coleman (Box 66, Folder 1-3)
    - Rosenthal, Macha (Box 66, Folder 4-5)
    - Roskolenko, Harry, Works (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Roskolenko, Correspondence (Box 66, Folder 7-8)
    - Rukeyser, Muriel, Poems (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Rukeyser, Other material (Box 66, Folder 10-11)
    - Sachs, David (Box 66, Folder 12-13)
    - Sale, William M, Jr. (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Salinger, Herman, Works (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Salinger, Correspondence (Box 66, Folder 16-17)
    - Salt, Sydney (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Sandburg, Carl (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Sandeen, Ernest (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Sandomirksy, Vera (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - Saroyan, William (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - Sarton, May, poems (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - Sarton, May, correspondence (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - Savage, D. S. (Box 66, Folder 25-27)
    - Schacht, Marshall (Box 67, Folder 1-2)
    - Schevill, James (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Schwartz, Delmore, Poems and Correspondence (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Schwartz, Prose (Box 67, Folder 5-6)
    - Schwartz, Selwyn (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Scott, Winfield T., Poems (Box 67, Folder 8-9)
    - Scott, Prose (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Scott, Prose (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Scott, Prose (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Scott, Winfield T, Correspondence SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Shapiro, Karl, Poems (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Shapiro, Poems (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Shapiro, Prose (Box 67, Folder 16-20)
    - Shapiro, Karl and Evalyn, correspondence (Box 67, Folder 21-26)
    - Shapiro, Leo (Box 68, Folder 1-2)
    - Shulenberger, Arvid (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Sitwell, Edith (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Smith, A.J.M., works (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Smith, A.J.M., correspondence (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Smith, Ray (Box 68, Folder 7-8)
    - Smith, W. J. Poems (Box 68, Folder 9-10)
    - Smith, W. J., Other material (Box 68, Folder 11-12)
    - Solomon, Marvin (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Spears, Monroe K. (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Spender, Stephen (Box 68, Folder 15-16)
    - Speyer, Leonora (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Squires, J. Radcliffe (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Stallman, Robert W. (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Stein, Gertrude (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Stepanchev, Stephen (Box 68, Folder 21-22)
    - Stephan, Ruth (Box 68, Folder 23-24)
    - Stevens, Wallace, Poems SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Stevens, Other material (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - Strobel, Marion, Poems (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - Strobel, Other material (Box 68, Folder 28)
    - Sutherland, John (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Swallow, Alan (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Sweeney, James John (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Symons, Julian (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Taggard, Genevieve SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Tate, Allen (Box 69, Folder 6-7)
    - Taylor, Frajam (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Theobald, John (includes Borgese poem (Box 69, Folder 9-10)
    - Thomas, Dylan (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Tietjens, Eunice (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Todd, Ruthven (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Tolson, M. B. (Box 69, Folder 14-15)
    - Treece, Henry (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Triem, Eve (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Tyler, Parker, Works (Box 69, Folder 18-19)
    - Tyler, Correspondence (Box 69, Folder 20-21)
    - Unger, Leonard (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - Untermeyer, Jean Starr (Box 69, Folder 23)
    - Van Duyn, Mona (Box 69, Folder 24-25)
    - Vazakas, Byron (Box 69, Folder 26-27)
    - Viereck, Peter, Works (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Viereck, Correspondence (Box 70, Folder 2-3)
    - Villa, Jose Garcia (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Vinal, Harold (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Wagoner, David (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Walton, Eda Lou (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Warren, Austin (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Warren, Robert Penn, works (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Warren, Robert Penn, correspondence SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Watkins, Vernon (Box 70, Folder 11-12)
    - Webster, Harvey Curtis (Box 70, Folder 13-14)
    - Weismiller, Edward (Box 70, Folder 15-16)
    - Weiss, T. (Box 70, Folder 17-18)
    - Wescott, Glenway (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - Wheelock, John Hall (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - Wheelwright, John (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - Whitely, Mary N. S. (Box 70, Folder 22-23)
    - Whittemore, Reed (Box 70, Folder 24)
    - Widdener, Margaret (Box 70, Folder 25)
    - Wilbur, Richard (Box 70, Folder 26-27)
    - Wilder, Thornton (Box 70, Folder 28)
    - Williams, Oscar, Works (Box 71, Folder 1-2)
    - Williams, Oscar, Correspondence (Box 71, Folder 3-4)
    - Williams, Oscar, Correspondence (Box 71, Folder 5-6)
    - Williams, Tennessee (some pieces are signed "Thomas Lanier Williams" instead of "Tennessee") (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Williams, William Carlos, Poems (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Williams, Prose (Box 71, Folder 9-10)
    - Williams, Correspondence (Box 71, Folder 11-12)
    - Wilson, Edmund (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Wilson, T. C. (Box 71, Folder 14-15)
    - Winters, Ivor, Poems (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Winters, Ivor, Prose (Box 71, Folder 17-18)
    - Winters, Ivor, Correspondence (Box 71, Folder 19-20)
    - Wyatt, Edith Franklin (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Zabel, Morton D. (Box 71, Folder 22-23)
    - Zaturenska, Marya (Box 71, Folder 24)
    - Zukofsky, Louis (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Subseries 2: Manuscripts - Minor Contributors
    - Aa-Ac, Aaen, Paul Abbott, Charles David Abel, Darrel Abel, Lionel Aby, Robert-Peter Acton, Ellen (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Ac-Am, Aczel, Peter (Aczel’s translations of Ady, Andrew) Adams, J. Donald Adriansen, Rolf Ageton, Arthur A. Ahmad, Mahmud Aivaz, David Akins, Zoe Alexander, Sheila Alexander, Sidney Algren, Nelson (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Al-Am, Allamand, Jacques Allen, Beth Allen, Charles Allen, Hervey Allen, Sara van Alstyne Allott, Kenneth Alyea, E. Dorothy Alsberg, Henry G. Amacher, Richard E. (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Am-An, Ames, Alfred C. Anderson, Douglas McClure Anderson, Jean (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - An, Anderson, Lee Anderson, Marcia Lee Anderson, Paul D. Anderson, Violet Anderson, Wendell Andre, Eugene Robert (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - An-Ar, Angadi, Ayana Deva Applebaum, Sydney Appel M.D., William Aquinas, Thomas, Sister SEE Thomas Aquinas, Sister Aragon, Louis (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Ar, Arberry, Arthur J. Archibald, R. C. Argraves, Hugh Armens, Sven Armstrong, Skeet Harris Armstrong, Virginia Irving Arnold, Theodor (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Ar-At, Arvay, Heinz Asher, Elise Asper, James E. Atkins, Elizabeth (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - At-Ax, Atkins, John Aubry, Edward T. Auerbach, Lee C. Austin, Mary Authors Guild Avery, Delos Aviles, Alonso Axelrod, Joseph (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Ba, Bacon, Leonard Bailey, Doris E. Bain, Read Balakian, Anna Balcom, Mrs. R.W. Ball Jr., Lee Ballard, Charles Bandeira, Manuel (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Ba, Bangs, Janet Norris Banks, Charles Barber, Mary Finette Barbour II, Thomas Barker, Eric Wilson (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Ba, Barnes, John W. Barrow, Elfrida Barry, Francis Barry, John D. Bartee, Darrell Bartlett, Elizabeth Bartra, Agusti (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Ba, Basler, Roy P. Bates. Margaret Bates, Scott Baum, Bernard Bayle, Rosalie (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Be, Beatty, John C. Beaudoin, Kenneth Lawrence Beck, Garrard Becker, Lucien Becker, Madeline L. Becker, William Beckwith, Russell (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Be, Beecher, John Beeching, Jack Bell, William Bellow, Barbara Beloof, Robert Belvin, William Benchley, [Robert] Benedict, Ruth Fulton Bengis, Jerome Benn, Gottfried Bennerson, Irving Leonard (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Be, Bennett, Joseph Benson, Corinne Bentley, Eric (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Be, Bentley, Nelson? Bergholz, Harr Bergman, Alexander F. Berhowitz, Robert L. Berlind, Bruce Bernetta, Lister Bernstein, Joseph M. (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Be, Berry, Virginia (Sister Mary St. Virginia) Bertocci, Angelo P. Betsky, Seymour (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Be-Bi, Beum, Robert Bezruc, Petr Biller, Matthew Bingham, Robert K. (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - Bi-Bl, Binney, James Binstock, Rabbi Louis Bird, Laura Lee Bittner, Nelson Del Bjerknes, Chris Black, John Blair, Arthur Blake, Howard Blake, Melissa (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - Bl, Bland, Edward Bley, E.S. Blish, James Bliss, Marion Louise (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - Bl-Bo, Bloch, Jean-Richard Block, Allan Blumenfield, Dr. Samuel M. Boas, George Bobrinskoy, George V. Bock, Frederick Bode, Carl (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - Bo, Bodenstein, Beatrice E. Bogardus, Edgar Bohm, Elizabeth Bohmbach, Marie Bolles, [?] Bomberger, Carl K. Bond, Donald F. (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - Bo, Bond, Judith S. Bond, Pearl Bondy, Barbara Bonnefoy, Yves Bonniwell, Mrs. Charles A. Boorum, Ted Boothe, James (Box 72, Folder 24)
    - Bo, Borja, Francisco Borrazzo, Benedict Borroff, Marie Borst, Richard Warner (Box 72, Folder 25)
    - Bose, Buddhadeva (Box 72, Folder 26)
    - Bo, Bosquet, Alain Bostelmann, ? Bottino, Dr. Salvatore Bourjaily, Vance Bowe. Julia (Box 72, Folder 27)
    - Bo-Br, Bowes Lyon, Lilian Bowles, Frances Bowman, Louise Morey Boyars, Arthur Boyce, McKinley Boyd, Julian P. Boyden, Polly Boyden, Sarah Bradbury, Bianca Bradbury, John Bradshaw, Jean H. (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Br, Brand, Millen Brecht, Bertolt Breé, Germaine Brewster, Elizabeth Bridson, D.G. Bright, Verne Brinkley, Maxine (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Br, Brittain, Robert Bromley, Priscilla Bronstein, Sidney Brooks, Jeremy Brotherton, J. L. Broughton, James Brown, John Lacey Brown, Kenneth Hunter Brown, Phyllis (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Br, Brown, Spencer Brown, Sterling A. Brown, Stuart Gerry Browne Jr., Aldis J. Browne, Anita Brownell, Baker Brownell, Florence Kerr Broxon, James W. Bruce, Charles Bruce, Irene (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Brussel, Clara (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Br-Bu, Bryan, Paul M. Bryant, Helen Bryant, Nelson Bryher, ? Brynes, Oscar Buchanan, Bessie Glen Buchler, Justus Buckley, Elizabeth L. Buechner, Frederick (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Bu, Buhrmann, June (Mrs. D.C.) Bulkley, Mary E. Bull, Arthur J. Burch, Claire Burden, Jean Burford, William, SEE Jacob, Max Burgener, R.J.C. Burgess, Virginia Burklund, Carl Edwin (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Bu-By, Burlin, Helen Burr, Gray Burrows, Edwin G. Butler, Charles E. Butler, Nan Buxton, John Bylansen, Stephen Byrne, Ellen H. (Box 73, Folder 8)